but we can't give up it's not a thing to give up on
because if you would know
how important gardening and farming is to
the economy of the country
and the global economy
if everybody had a little Home Garden
you know first thing
the entire earth would be cooler
there are a lot of houses that don't have
any plants
at all
if all those houses
didn't have plants
had plants!
global temperature would
would normalize
right that's the first thing the economy itself
a lot of money you spend...
in the markets
farmers have to extend themselves
and use methods that they really don't want to use
to produce the quantity
why do they have to produce such a large quantity?
because people aren't growing
what they need at home and if they were doing that
then you know
globally we'd have healthier food
we'd have food unique to each person
you get what I'm saying
gardening and farming are very important so
when people give up on these things
you know
it's not just a personal thing
it affect us as a human family
it affect